boticca.com 2019-07-25

# Privacy & Cookies Policy | Help | Wolf & Badger

This webpage sets out when and how we use your personal information that you or others provide to us.

We are Wolf & Badger, a limited company with registration number 06980629. Our registered address is 10 Queen Street Place, London, United Kingdom, EC4R 1AG.

We have appointed a Data Protection Manager who is responsible for overseeing questions in relation to this privacy notice. If you have any questions about this privacy notice, including any requests to exercise your legal rights, please contact our Data Protection Manager by email at [support@wolfandbadger.com](mailto:support@wolfandbadger.com).

### **How do you use my data?**

### **When you purchase products from our website or from in store**

We collect:

| 

Your name, address, email address, phone number and payment details.  
  
---|---  
  
Our lawful basis:

| 

Our legitimate interest to help conclude the contract you have entered into with the seller.  
  
Who we share it with:

| 

We share your personal information with our subcontractors who are involved in the purchase process, such as payment providers, as well as credit reference agencies who we use to assess fraud, credit and/or security risks. The seller you have purchased from also receives your name, address and contact details so they can deliver your order (if applicable) and help resolve any customer service queries you have. Our sellers are under strict instructions and binding contracts to only use your personal information to deliver your order, if applicable, and help resolve any customer service queries you have.  
  
### **When you contact us or talk to us via live chat for customer service purposes**

We collect:

| 

Your name, contact details and the other details you provide to us.  
  
---|---  
  
Our lawful basis:

| 

We provide customer services because we have a legitimate interest in wanting to assist you receive the best service possible.   
  
Who we share it with:

| 

Olark, our live chat provider. But they can only use the personal information they hold in accordance with our instructions.  
  
### **When you have expressed an interest in our products**

We collect:

| 

Your name, email address, postal address, telephone number and sector preferences.  
  
---|---  
  
Our lawful basis:

| 

When we send you marketing emails because you have opted-in to receive them, we rely on your consent to contact you for marketing purposes. 

If you have not opted-in and we send you marketing emails,  and when we use Facebook Custom Audiences and Google’s Retargeting lists, we do this because of our legitimate interest to promote the success of our business.

You can tell us that you do not want your personal information to be processed in this way at any time by contacting us at support@wolfandbadger.com or, where relevant, by following the unsubscribe link shown in every marketing communication you receive from us.

If you have opted out of our email marketing, you may still continue to see target ads on social media platforms. Please check the social media platforms for more details on how to opt out of seeing these ads.  
  
Who we share it with:

| 

Facebook and Google for retargeting.

We also share your personal information with our subcontractors who help us electronic marketing platforms  
  
### **If you are a brand talking to us about, or selling on our website**

We collect:

| 

Your name, address, email address, phone number and payment details, as well as information about your products.  
  
---|---  
  
Our lawful basis:

| 

If you are not yet selling on our site, our lawful basis is our legitimate interest to encourage sellers to use our site. If you are an active seller with us, then our lawful basis is to enter into a perform the contract between us.  
  
Who we share it with:

| 

Our professional advisors when required for tax, regulatory, legal and accounting purposes.  
  
### **To improve and secure our website**

We collect:

| 

IP address, browser type, device type, referring website.   
  
---|---  
  
Our lawful basis:

| 

Our legitimate interest to provide you with the best experience we can, and to ensure that our site is kept secure.   
  
Who we share it with:

| 

The service providers identified in the cookies table below.  
  
### **If our business is sold**

What details we may transfer

| 

If Wolf & Badger or the majority of its assets are acquired by somebody else, your personal information held by us will be transferred to the buyer.   
  
---|---  
  
Our lawful basis:

| 

We process your personal information for this purpose because we have a legitimate interest to ensure our business can be continued by the buyer. If you object to our use of your personal information in this way, the buyer of our business may not be able to provide services to you.

In some circumstances we may also need to share your personal information if we are under a duty to disclose or share it to comply with a legal obligation.   
  
Who we share it with:

| 

The purchaser of our business and our professional advisors (such as lawyers and accountants).  
  
### ****

### **Cookies**

Our site uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our site and also allows us to improve our site. By continuing to browse the site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.

A cookies is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer. We use the following cookies:

**Cookie**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---  
  
**Google Analytics**

| 

This is a web analytics service, which allows us to track the use of the Website, prepare reports on user activity and share them with other Google services ([privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/); [opt-out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)).  
  
**Ometria**

| 

This is a web analytics service, which allows us to track the use of the Website ([privacy policy](https://www.ometria.com/privacy-policy))  
  
**Qubit**

| 

This is a personalisation service ([privacy policy](https://www.qubit.com/legal/privacy-and-cookie-policy/)).  
  
**Criteo**

| 

This is an online advertising and remarketing service ([privacy policy](https://www.criteo.com/privacy/); [opt-out](https://www.criteo.com/privacy/)).  
  
**Sift**

| 

This is a fraud and malicious behaviour detection service ([privacy policy](https://siftscience.com/service-privacy)).  
  
**PayPal**

| 

This service processes payments for us ([privacy policy](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full#2)).  
  
**Hotjar**

| 

This is a screen recording service ([privacy policy](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy%C2%A0))  
  
**Olark**

| 

This is a live chat customer support service ([privacy policy](https://www.olark.com/privacy-policy/)).  
  
**Olapic**

| 

This service collects user generated content for us ([privacy policy](http://www.olapic.com/privacy-policy/)).  
  
**Facebook**

| 

This provides an online advertising and remarketing service for us ([privacy policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update)).  
  
**SkimLinks**

| 

This is an affiliate service ([privacy policy](https://skimlinks.com/privacy-policy)).  
  
**Pinterest**

| 

This is a conversion tracking service for us ([privacy policy](https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy)).  
  
Please note that third parties (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) may also use cookies, which we do not have any control over. These cookies are likely to be analytical/performance cookies or targeting cookies.

You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our site. 

Except for essential cookies, all cookies will expire after 2 years.

### ****

### **Where is my data stored?**

Some of our external third parties are based outside the European Economic Area (EEA) so their processing of your personal information will involve a transfer of data outside of the EEA.

Whenever we transfer your personal information outside of the EEA, we ensure it is protected by making sure at least one of the following safeguards is in place:

  * by transferring your personal information to a country that has been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection by the European Commission;
  * by using specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give your personal information the same protection it has within the EEA; and
  * where we use providers based in the US, we may transfer data to them if they are part of the Privacy Shield which requires them to provide similar protection to personal data shared between Europe and the US.

To keep this privacy policy as short and easy to understand as possible, we have not set out the specific circumstances when each of these protection measures are used. You can contact us at support@wolfandbadger.com for the details as to how we protect specific transfer of your data.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers or those of our third party data storage providers. 

### ****

### **How long do we retain your data for?**

We will only retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting or legal requirements

To determine the appropriate retention period for the personal information we hold, we consider the amount, nature and sensitivity of the personal information, the risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal information, the reasons why we handle your personal information and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

In some circumstances (to understand purchasing trends and how people interact with our website) we may anonymise your personal data so that it can no longer be associated with you for research or statistical purposes, in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.

### ****

### **What are my rights under data protection laws?**

**Request access** to your data (commonly known as a "subject access request"). This enables you to receive a copy of the data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.

**Request correction** of the data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate information we hold about you corrected.

**Request erasure** of your data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove data where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to 

delete or remove your data where you have exercised your right to object to processing (see below).

**Object to processing** of your data where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground. You also have the right to object where we are processing your data for direct marketing purposes, research or statistical purposes.

**Request the restriction** of processing of your data. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of data about you, for example if you want us to establish its accuracy or the reason for processing it.

**Request the transfer** of your data to another party. 

Privacy law is often complicated, and whether these rights are available to you sometimes depends on the types of data we are handling, as well as why we are handling it. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us using the details at the bottom of this notice. You always have the right to lodge a complaint with us or the Information Commissioner's Office, the supervisory authority for data protection issues in England and Wales.

### ****

### **What about websites we link to?**

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks and affiliates.  

Our site connects you to different websites.  If you follow a link to any of these websites or use our services, please note that you have left our site and these websites have their own privacy policies.  

We do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies or websites.  Please check their policies before you submit any personal information to these websites.

### ****

### **When will you change your privacy policy?**

Any changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail or post.

Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.

### ****

### **How do I contact you with feedback?**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to our Data Protection Manager at support@wolfandbadger.com.

_This privacy policy was last updated on 14 June 2019._
